hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Where's the other one?
Hey...
Who are you looking for?
I'll take care of the rest.
Go wash your eyes in that river.
This is my ability...
specializing in assassination of course.
You can't beat me by just having
a good nose and nails...
You can't beat my ability!
Akamaru... I'm sorry...
Akamaru...
We've always done things together.
We were together
whenever and wherever.
However this one time I'm sunk.
My cells can swim inside
your body as I wish
and I can even create parts
that are only you.
In other words,
a little bit of a fusion condition...
a sharing of the flesh is what it'll be.
A sharing...?
That's right!
And a cruel way of killing
that only I can accomplish...
the gradual scraping off
of just your cells!
I see...
If that's the case...!
If I do this...
what's gonna happen?
Suicide?! That's ridiculous!
Die with me...
Everyone's Fight
What are you thinking?!
It's just as I thought...
We are sharing one body, right?
Damn it!
Entering my opponent's body
to avoid any attacks...
that is my Jutsu's greatest advantage.
There hasn't been
a single one before now
who's done this sort of thing.
Are you in pain?
All right then, let's get comfortable now.
Yikes, you idiot!
Stop it!
It's too late!
There's not enough blood...
Damn!
Damn...
Where'd he go?
So he left his little dog behind
and fled.
It's the right decision,
but he's more cold-hearted than me.
What?!
It couldn't be!
What a relief...
He's still breathing.
What a relief!
Akamaru... You really gave it your best.
Because of you I was able to hold up
the enemy for a while.
We've caused injuries
upon the enemy too.
It's enough... You've done enough.
His name is Akamaru.
Huh?
Mom... Nee-chan...
From today you'll take care of him...
Okay?
I will?
I'm Kiba. Nice to meet you, Akamaru.
You!
We've been together forever.
Nice catch, Akamaru!
All right, you did well!
Here we go!
Be more serious about it!
Stop being such a baby!
Mom...
Listen, Kiba...
It's not just you.
Akamaru and you,
the two of you need
to become strong together.
With Akamaru... Together?
Akamaru...
That's right.
Way to go, Akamaru! You did it!
Mid-air Dynamic Marking!
Next is mid-air triple somersault!
Take your aim!
Yahoo!
We'll be together forever
from now on too...
I'll protect you from now on!
That jerk!
Setting up a trap on me!
I'll kill you!
Hey! Sakon! Where are you?! Sakon!
Sakon!
Blah, blah, blah.
You're such a nuisance, aniki.
Your yelling stings my eyes...
Aniki!
I'll kill him... is what I'd like to do
but it's almost time for my sleep.
Capture those bastards alive in my place.
When I wake up
I'll kill them.
All right, Sakon?
Capture them alive...
Yeah, I got it...
But...
The killing part
we'll do it together.
If I carelessly attack,
he dodges
and I end up attacking myself!
Behold!
Willow Dance!
You!
Bones?
This is my... Kekkei Genkai.
What's with this guy...?
Is he attacking with bones sticking out
from all over his body?
He's grabbed his own bone!
It'll be soon...
He's turning the bone...
into a sword!
It's futile. It's not just ordinary bone.
The highest density bone is hard as steel.
So what?! I'll break that bone!
I possess Five Dances.
You'd better not think
you know my strength after just this much.
What?!
I'll specially show you...
the Camellia Dance next.
Come!
I'll crush you!
I did it!
It's a Substitution?!
There!
Damn!
They're getting closer and closer.
This isn't good, traces of blood!
Damn, I did save Akamaru
for the time being
but maybe I went too far.
This smell...
What does it mean?
Why... Why is it that even those guys
are headed to a place like this?!
I don't understand anymore.
In any case,
we need to leave this place quickly.
I can't...
I'm starting to feel light-headed
from the pain and loss of blood...
My body won't move at all either...
Akamaru...
He left just his coat...
Huh?
So he fled by floating down the river...
Damn!
Damn...
This is it!
So I've cornered you, you stinking rat!
Pretty impressive...
You timed it well to scatter
the three to attack.
You must have practiced quite a bit, huh?
Since it's a pretty complicated song...
Well now...
Not only did you
immediately understand
that I'm manipulating these guys
with my flute
you understood how difficult this song is.
You're a pretty impressive punk.
But you can't completely
understand this song.
You're so right...
since art is so foreign to me.
But since she uses that flute
to manipulate
it means that song must contain
individually specific sound patterns
to control each and every movement
of those guys.
I'm pretty confident
when it comes to just analyzing
but this time it's not looking good.
The reason is that
I don't understand
musical notes whatsoever.
There's no one that's heard
this song and lived.
Finale Ninth Passage
Demon Revolution!
The melody's changed!
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
Attacks and defense without gaps
using three Summoned bodies.
I hate to admit but she may
be a pretty good Shogi player.
Plus, I don't have much Ninja tools left...
Man, it feels like I'm playing
without rooks or bishops.
Now then... shall I go?
Cry or laugh,
I can only give it my all here!
Next time:
"Fake! Man Shikamaru Gambles to Recover From a Hopeless Situation."